<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[A Peek at Computer Electronics]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Are you a programmer or computer enthusiast? Do you feel comfortable with methods, functions, and variables? Do you wish you knew more about how the computer made it all work? Now you can. From basic electronics to advanced computer hardware, you'll learn the magic behind the gear that makes it all run.
  
  If you're into tinkering, or ever thought about it, this book explains the basics of how it all works. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Caleb Tennis]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/a_peek_at_computer_electronics.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Advanced Rails Recipes]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[With the help of a community of Rails chefs in the kitchen, here are 84 new ways to kick your Rails apps up a notch. Advanced Rails Recipes is a collection of practical recipes for spicing up your web application without a lot of prep and cleanup. You'll learn how the pros have solved the tough problems using the most up-to-date Rails 2 techniques so you can deliver your stunning web app quicker and easier. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Mike Clark]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/advanced_rails_recipes.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Agile Web Development with Rails, 3rd Edition]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Rails just keeps on changing. Rails 3 and Ruby 1.9 bring hundreds of improvements, including new APIs and substantial performance enhancements. The fourth edition of this award-winning classic has been reorganized and refocused so it's more useful than ever before for developers new to Ruby and Rails. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Sam Ruby, Dave Thomas, David Heinemeier Hansson]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/agile_web_development_with_rails_3rd_edition.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Agile Web Development with Rails, 4th Edition]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Rails just keeps on changing. Rails 3 and Ruby 1.9 bring hundreds of improvements, including new APIs and substantial performance enhancements. The fourth edition of this award-winning classic has been reorganized and refocused so it's more useful than ever before for developers new to Ruby and Rails.
  
  Rails 3 is a major release the changes aren't just incremental, but structural. So we decided to follow suit. This book isn't just a mild reworking of the previous edition to make it run with the new Rails. Instead, it's a complete refactoring.
  
  You'll still find the Depot example at the front, but you'll also find testing knitted right in. Gone are the long reference chapters that's what the web does best. Instead you'll find more targeted information on all the aspects of Rails that you'll need to be a successful Web developer. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Sam Ruby]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/agile_web_development_with_rails_4th_edition.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Arduino]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Arduino is an open-source platform that makes DIY electronics projects easier than ever. Readers with no electronics experience can create their first gadgets within a few minutes. This book is up-to-date for the new Arduino Uno board, with step-by-step instructions for building a universal remote, a motion-sensing game controller, and many other fun, useful projects. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Maik Schmidt]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/arduino.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Beginning Mac Programming]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[You already know the reasons to get into Mac programming: millions of users rely on the Mac as their primary operating system. If you are searching for a new job, acquiring a skill set, or simply inspired to develop software for the Mac, Beginning Mac Programming is the practical and straightforward introduction to the basics you need to create innovative applications that people will seek out, discuss, and rely on. Beginners welcome! ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Tim Isted]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/beginning_mac_programming.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Behind Closed Doors]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Great management is difficult to see as it occurs. Great management happens in one-on-one meetings and with other managers all in private. It's hard to learn management by example when you can't see it.
  
  Find out what goes on Behind Closed Doors and see how a skilled manager turns around a tricky management situation in seven weeks. You'll learn how to provide and use feedback effectively, and become a better coach and mentor peers and team members. As you begin to build a cohesive, "jelled" team you'll learn how to use your influence across the organization and make better choices daily to survive and thrive. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Johanna Rothman, Esther Derby]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/behind_closed_doors.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Best of Ruby Quiz]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Sharpen your Ruby programming skills with twenty-five challenging problems from Ruby Quiz. Read the problems, work out a solution, and compare your solution with others. This book is a collection of highlights from the first year of Ruby Quiz challenges. Inside, you will find expanded content, all new solutions, and more in depth discussions of Ruby Quiz problems and solutions. This is the book for anyone who really wants to improve their Ruby skills. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[James Edward Gray II]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/best_of_ruby_quiz.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Cocoa Programming]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Cocoa frameworks let you write powerful and attractive applications for Mac OS X or the iPhone. With this book plus your existing knowledge of object-oriented programming you can take advantage of Cocoa and create compelling, feature rich, compliant Mac applications for this industry-leading environment using XCode 3. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Daniel H Steinberg]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/cocoa_programming.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Code in the Cloud]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Join the next wave of Web 2.0 software development in the cloud! Cloud applications are the next big shift in application development: instead of building single-user applications to run on a personal computer, new applications are being built as multi-user services that run in data centers around the world. One of the most exciting new environments for building services in the cloud is Google's AppEngine. AppEngine is a powerful, easy-to-use framework for developing cloud-based services. This book will teach you what you need to make the shift to cloud development using AppEngine. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Mark C. Chu-Carroll]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/code_in_the_cloud.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Continuous Testing]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Feedback. We're always telling you that you need feedback, with a short feedback gap the time it takes to get feedback on your decisions, your code, your designs. Well, what if you narrowed the feedback gap to near zero while coding? You'd have continuous testing, a powerful idea that lets you fix bugs while they're still small and fresh.
  
  Continuous Testing shows you how to use a combination of tests, tools, and techniques to immediately detect problems in code, before they spread. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Ben Rady, Rod Coffin]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/continuous_testing.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Core Animation for Mac OS X and the iPhone]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Have you seen Apple's Front Row application and Cover Flow effects? Then you've seen Core Animation at work. It's about making applications that give strong visual feedback through movement and morphing, rather than repainting panels. This comprehensive guide will get you up to speed quickly and take you into the depths of this new technology. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Bill Dudney]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/core_animation_for_mac_os_x_and_the_iphone.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Core Data]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Learn the Apple Core Data APIs from the ground up. With Core Data, you can concentrate on designing the model for your application, and use the power of Core Data to do the rest. This book will take you from Core Data fundamentals to expert configurations that you will not find anywhere else. Together we'll walk through a fullfeatured application based on the Mac OS X Core Data API. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Marcus S. Zarra]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/core_data.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Crafting Rails Applications]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Rails 3 is a huge step forward. You can now easily extend the framework, change its behavior, and replace whole components to bend it to your will, all without messy hacks. This pioneering book is the first resource that deep dives into the new Rails 3 APIs and shows you how to use them to write better web applications and make your day-to-day work with Rails more productive. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Jose Valim]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/crafting_rails_applications.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Debug It!]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Professional programmers develop a knack of unerringly zeroing in on the root cause of a bug. They can do that because they've written a lot of buggy code and then gained experience fixing it. This book captures all this experience - use it, and you'll find you write fewer bugs, and the ones you do write will become easier to hunt down. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Paul Butcher]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/debug_it.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Design Accessible Web Sites]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA["Accessibility" has a reputation of being dull, dry, and unfriendly toward graphic design. But there is a better way: well-styled semantic markup that lets you provide the best possible results for all of your users. This book will help you provide images, video, Flash and PDF in an accessible way that looks great to your sighted users, but is still accessible to all users. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Jeremy Sydik]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/design_accessible_web_sites.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Driving Technical Change]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[If you work with people, you need this book. Learn to read co-workers and users patterns of resistance and dismantle their objections. With these techniques and strategies you can master the art of evangelizing and help your organization adopt your solutions. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Terrence Ryan]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/driving_technical_change.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Enterprise Integration with Ruby]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Learn how the power and elegance of Ruby can make it easier to get enterprise-level applications to work together. See how Ruby can be used as the glue to combine applications in new ways, extending their lives and increasing their (and your) value to your company. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Maik Schmidt]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/enterprise_integration_with_ruby.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Enterprise Recipes with Ruby and Rails]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Every web site project is really an enterprise integration project in disguise. Ruby on Rails makes it easier than ever to create complex and good-looking web sites, but there's plenty of life beyond the rails. The 50+ recipes in this book not only show you how to integrate lurking legacy material using Ruby and Ruby on Rails, but also how to create new and highly functional applications in an enterprise environment. You can build completely new applications by enhancing and combining existing components in creative, compelling new ways. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Maik Schmidt]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/enterprise_recipes_with_ruby_and_rails.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Everyday Scripting with Ruby]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Are you a tester who spends more time manually creating complex test data than using it? A business analyst who seemingly went to college all those years so you can spend your days copying data from reports into spreadsheets? A programmer who can't finish each day's task without having to scan through version control system output, looking for the file you want?
  
  If so, you're wasting that computer on your desk. Offload the drudgery to where it belongs, and free yourself to do what you should be doing: thinking. All you need is a scripting language (free!), this book (cheap!), and the dedication to work through the examples and exercises. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Brian Marick]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/everyday_scripting_with_ruby.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[ExpressionEngine 2]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Whether you're building a small site or a large corporate undertaking, ExpressionEngine is becoming the tool of choice. With this Quick-Start Guide, you'll get hands-on experience with ExpressionEngine 2 by building a complete web site from start to finish. You'll learn techniques and best practices for customizing and optimizing your sites, including working with new ExpressionEngine 2 features, templates, and site search. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Ryan Irelan]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/expressionengine_2.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[From Java To Ruby]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[You want your development team to be productive. You want to write flexible, maintainable web applications. You want to use Ruby and Rails. But can you justify the move away from established platforms such as J2EE? Bruce Tate's From Java to Ruby has the answers, and it expresses them in a language that'll help persuade managers and executives who've seen it all. See when and where the switch makes sense, and see how to make it. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Bruce Tate]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/from_java_to_ruby.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[FXRuby]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[FXRuby is one of the most popular libraries for developing graphical user interface applications in Ruby. This book is the quickest and easiest way to get started developing GUI applications using FXRuby. With a combination of tutorial exercises and focused, technical information, this book goes beyond the basics to equip you with proven, practical knowledge and techniques for developing real-world FXRuby applications. Learn directly from the lead developer of FXRuby and you'll be writing powerful and sophisticated GUIs in your favorite programming language. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Lyle Johnson]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/fxruby.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[GIS for Web Developers]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[There is a hidden revolution going on: geography is moving from niche to the mainstream. GIS for Web Developers introduces Geographic Information Systems (GIS) in simple terms and demonstrates hands-on uses. With this book, you'll explore popular websites like maps.google.com, see the technologies they use, and learn how to create your own. Written with the usual Pragmatic Bookshelf humor and real-world experience, GIS for Web Developers makes geographic programming concepts accessible to the common developer. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Scott Davis]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/gis_for_web_developers.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Google Maps API, 2nd Edition]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[This is the second edition of this Friday, which has been rewritten to use the Google Maps V2 API. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Scott Davis]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/google_maps_api_2nd_edition.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Grails]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Java web development is notoriously tedious, but help is on the way: Grails. Using the principle of convention-over-configuration and the dynamic Groovy programming language, Grails takes the pain out of web development and brings back the fun. This book will get you up and running with Grails by putting it to use in constructing an original, working application from start to finish. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Dave Klein]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/grails.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Groovy Recipes]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[If you're a busy Java professional who needs quick solutions to everyday problems, then Groovy Recipes is for you. The Groovy language and Grails web framework give you seamless integration with your legacy Java code while adding the flexibility and dynamism of a scripting language and giving you modern, agile, time-saving techniques. Groovy allows you to write code the way you always thought you should - you'll never look at Java the same way again. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Scott Davis]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/groovy_recipes.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Hello, Android, 3rd Edition]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Google's Android is shaking up the mobile market in a big way. With Android, you can write programs that run on any compatible cell phone in the world. It's a mobile platform you can't afford not to learn, and this book gets you started. This third edition covers all Android versions from Android 1.5 to Android 2. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Ed Burnette]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/hello,_android_3rd_edition.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[HTML5 and CSS3]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[HTML5 and CSS3 are the future of web development, but you don't have to wait to start using them. Even though the specification is still in development, many modern browsers and mobile devices already support HTML5 and CSS3. This book gets you up to speed on the new HTML5 elements and CSS3 features you can use right now, and backwards compatible solutions ensure that you don't leave users of older browsers behind. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Brian P. Hogan]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/html5_and_css3.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Interface Oriented Design]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Learn by pragmatic example how to create effective designs composed of interfaces to objects, components and services.
  
  You'll learn what polymorphism and encapsulation really mean, and how to use these ideas more effectively. See how to create better interfaces using agile development techniques, and learn the subtle differences between implementing an interface and inheriting an implementation. Take a fresh, modern view of Design By Contract and class responsibilities. Understand the basis of a service-oriented architecture, including stateful versus stateless interfaces, procedural versus document models, and synchronous versus asynchronous invocations. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Ken Pugh]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/interface_oriented_design.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[iOS Recipes]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Take your iPhone and iPad apps to the next level. You've seen cool features and tricks in other apps, but haven't had the time to really look into how they're done. We've got the answers for you. This book walks you through clean, reusable solutions to a wide variety of problems and patterns common to iOS development with Cocoa Touch and Objective-C. With these recipes in your arsenal, your next apps will be more polished and more maintainable than ever. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Paul Warren, Matt Drance]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/ios_recipes.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[iPad Programming]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[It's not an iPhone and it's not a laptop: the iPad is a groundbreaking new device. You need to create true iPad apps to take advantage of all that is possible with the iPad. If you're an experienced iPhone developer, iPad Programming will show you how to write these outstanding new apps while completely fitting your users expectation for this device. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Daniel H Steinberg, Eric T Freeman]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/ipad_programming.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[iPhone SDK Development]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Jump into application development for today's most remarkable mobile communications platform, the Pragmatic way, with iPhone SDK Development. This Pragmatic guide takes you through the tools and APIs, the same ones Apple uses for its applications, that you can use to create your own software for the iPhone and iPod touch. Packed with useful examples, this book will give you both the big-picture concepts and the everyday "gotcha" details that developers need to make the most of the beauty and power of the iPhone OS platform. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Bill Dudney, Chris Adamson]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/iphone_sdk_development.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Land the Tech Job You Love]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[You've got the technical chops - the skills to get a great job doing what you love. Now it's time to get down to the business of planning your job search, focusing your time and attention on the job leads that matter, and interviewing to wow your boss-to-be. Land the tech job you love. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Andy Lester]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/land_the_tech_job_you_love.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Language Implementation Patterns]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Learn to build configuration file readers, data readers, model-driven code generators, source-to-source translators, source analyzers, and interpreters. You don't need a background in computer science - ANTLR creator Terence Parr demystifies language implementation by breaking it down into the most common design patterns. Pattern by pattern, you'll learn the key skills you need to implement your own computer languages. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Terence Parr]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/language_implementation_patterns.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Learn to Program, 2nd Edition]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[For this new edition of the best-selling Learn to Program, Chris Pine has taken a good thing and made it even better. First, he used the feedback from hundreds of reader e-mails to update the content and make it even clearer. Second, he updated the examples in the book to use the latest stable version of Ruby, and also to use code that looks more like real-world Ruby code, so that people who have just learned to program will be more familiar with common Ruby techniques.
  
  Not only does the Second Edition now include answers to all of the exercises, it includes them twice. First you'll find the "how you could do it" answers, using the techniques you've learned up to that point in the book. Next you'll see "how Chris Pine would do it": answers using more advanced Ruby techniques, to whet your appetite as well as providing sort of a "Rosetta Stone" for more elegant solutions. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Chris Pine]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/learn_to_program_2nd_edition.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Manage It!]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[This book is a reality - based guide for modern projects. You'll learn how to recognize your project's potholes and ruts, and determine the best way to fix problems - without causing more problems. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Johanna Rothman]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/manage_it.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Manage Your Project Portfolio]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Too many projects? Want to organize them and evaluate them without getting buried under a mountain of statistics? This book will help you collect all your work, decide which projects you should do first, second and never. You'll see how to tie your work to your organization's mission and show your board, your managers, and your staff what you can accomplish and when. You'll get a better view of the work you have, and learn how to make those difficult decisions, ensuring that all your strength is focused where it needs to be. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Johanna Rothman]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/manage_your_project_portfolio.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Mastering Dojo]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Imagine a true thin-client web application environment, with no browser incompatibilities, no plugins, and an interface that's closer to a desktop app. You can have it all, today. Welcome to The Dojo Toolkit.
  
  Mastering Dojo walks you through the whole range of modern web programming problems, from bringing simple web pages to life with widgets and animation, to designing and building an enterprise-class, single-page Rich Internet Application (RIA).
  
  Are your web pages becoming more and more complex, with hundreds of lines of sprawling JavaScript as clients demand modern Ajax designs? Or maybe you're about to enter the new world of single-page, Rich Internet Applications? Dojo is the unified toolkit that you need to get the job done. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Craig Riecke, Rawld Gill, Alex Russell]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/mastering_dojo.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Metaprogramming Ruby]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[As a Ruby programmer, you already know how much fun it is. Now see how to unleash its power, digging under the surface and exploring the language's most advanced features: a collection of techniques and tricks known as metaprogramming. Once the domain of expert Rubyists, metaprogramming is now accessible to programmers of all levels from beginner to expert. Metaprogramming Ruby explains metaprogramming concepts in a down-to-earth style and arms you with a practical toolbox that will help you write great Ruby code. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Paolo Perrotta]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/metaprogramming_ruby.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Modular Java]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Attack complexity in your Java applications using Modular Java. This pragmatic guide introduces you to OSGi and Spring Dynamic Modules, two of the most compelling frameworks for Java modularization. Driven by real-world examples, this book will equip you with the know-how you need to develop Java applications that are composed of smaller, loosely coupled, highly cohesive modules. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Craig Walls]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/modular_java.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[No Fluff Just Stuff 2006 Anthology]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Take 13 of the world's best trainers and speakers and ask them to write a chapter on something they care passionately about. The result? A book on software development unlike any other. Fifteen chapters covering the range of modern software development topics, from Domain-Specific Languages through Aspect-Oriented CSS to learning from the past. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Neal Ford (ed)]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/no_fluff_just_stuff_2006_anthology.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Practical Programming]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Welcome to computer science in the 21st century. Did you ever wonder how computers represent DNA? How they can download a web page containing population data and analyze it to spot trends? Or how they can change the colors in a color photograph? If so, this book is for you. By the time you're done, you'll know how to do all of that and a lot more. And Python makes it easy and fun. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Jennifer Campbell, Paul Gries, Jason Montojo, Greg]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/practical_programming.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Practices of an Agile Developer]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Want to be a better developer? This book collects the personal habits, ideas, and approaches of successful agile software developers and presents them in a series of short, easy-to-digest tips.
  
  You'll learn how to improve your software development process, see what real agile practices feel like, avoid the common temptations that kill projects, and keep agile practices in balance. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Venkat Subramaniam, Andy Hunt]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/practices_of_an_agile_developer.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Pragmatic Guide to Git]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Need to learn how to wrap your head around Git, but don't need a lot of hand holding? Grab this book if you're new to Git, not to the world of programming. Git tasks displayed on two-page spreads provide all the context you need, without the extra fluff. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Travis Swicegood]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/pragmatic_guide_to_git.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Pragmatic Guide to JavaScript]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[JavaScript is everywhere. It's a key component of today's Web a powerful, dynamic language with a rich ecosystem of professional-grade development tools, infrastructures, frameworks, and toolkits. This book will get you up to speed quickly and painlessly with the 35 key JavaScript tasks you need to know. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Christophe Porteneuve]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/pragmatic_guide_to_javascript.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Pragmatic Guide to Subversion]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Subversion is the most popular open-source version control system on the planet. Development teams-big and small, enterprise and open source-use this fast, feature-rich tool daily. Pragmatic Guide to Subversion presents the 48 essential tasks you need to know. It's your shortcut to the Subversion master's recommended set of best practices. With this book, you can get to the good parts quickly, and be more productive and effective. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Mike Mason]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/pragmatic_guide_to_subversion.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Pragmatic Project Automation]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Pragmatic Project Automation shows you how to improve the consistency and repeatability of your project's procedures using automation to reduce risk and errors.
  
  Simply put, we're going to put this thing called a computer to work for you doing the mundane (but important) project stuff. That means you'll have more time and energy to do the really exciting and difficult stuff, like writing quality code. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Mike Clark]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/pragmatic_project_automation.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Pragmatic Thinking and Learning]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Software development happens in your head. Not in an editor, IDE, or design tool. You're well educated on how to work with software and hardware, but what about wetware our own brains? Learning new skills and new technology is critical to your career, and it's all in your head.
  
  In this book by Andy Hunt, you'll learn how our brains are wired, and how to take advantage of your brain's architecture. You'll learn new tricks and tips to learn more, faster, and retain more of what you learn.
  
  You need a pragmatic approach to thinking and learning. You need to Refactor Your Wetware. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Andy Hunt]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/pragmatic_thinking_and_learning.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Pragmatic Unit Testing in C# with NUnit, 2nd Edition]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Pragmatic programmers use feedback to drive their development and personal processes. The most valuable feedback you can get while coding comes from unit testing. Now in it's second edition, Pragmatic Unit Testing in C# with NUnit, 2nd Ed. will show you how to do software unit testing, of course, but more importantly will show you what to test. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Andy Hunt, Dave Thomas, Matt Hargett]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/pragmatic_unit_testing_in_c_with_nunit_2nd_edition.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Pragmatic Unit Testing in Java with JUnit]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Pragmatic programmers use feedback to drive their development and personal processes. The most valuable feedback you can get while coding comes from unit testing.
  
  Let your Java code tell you what's working and what isn't. You'll learn how to test using JUnit, but more importantly, you'll learn what to test. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Alasdair Allan]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/pragmatic_unit_testing_in_java_with_junit.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Pragmatic Version Control using CVS]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Pragmatic Version Control is available in two different flavors: using CVS and using Subversion. Click on the links to each book for more details, code from the books, errata, reviews, ordering information, sample chapters, and a free printable summary card. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Dave Thomas, Andy Hunt]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/pragmatic_version_control_using_cvs.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Pragmatic Version Control Using Git]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[There's a change in the air. High-profile projects such as the Linux Kernel, Mozilla, Gnome, and Ruby on Rails are now using Distributed Version Control Systems (DVCS) instead of the old stand-bys of CVS or Subversion.
  
  Git is a modern, fast DVCS. But understanding how it fits into your development can be a daunting task without an introduction to the new concepts. Whether you're just starting out as a professional programmer or are an old hand, this book will get you started using Git in this new distributed world. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Travis Swicegood]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/pragmatic_version_control_using_git.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Pragmatic Version Control using Subversion, 2nd Edition]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Revised content to reflect all the major changes to Subversion 1.3 New chapter on Subversion's optional file locking to help you manage unmergeable binary files New sections covering path-based security for both the svnserve and Apache networking servers New advanced topics chapter covering programmatic access to Subversion and advanced repository management. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Mike Mason]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/pragmatic_version_control_using_subversion_2nd_edition.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Programming Clojure]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[If you are a Java programmer, if you care about concurrency, or if you enjoy working in low-ceremony language such as Ruby or Python, Programming Clojure is for you. Clojure is a general-purpose language with direct support for Java, a modern Lisp dialect, and support in both the language and data structures for functional programming. Programming Clojure shows you how to write applications that have the beauty and elegance of a good scripting language, the power and reach of the JVM, and a modern, concurrency-safe functional style. Now you can write beautiful code that runs fast and scales well. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Stuart Halloway]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/programming_clojure.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Programming Cocoa with Ruby]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Programming Cocoa with Ruby brings together two enthusiastic development communities. Ruby programmers will tell you how productive they are with just the right amount of code. Cocoa developers know the importance of a clean, intuitive interface.
  
  Now, through Programming Cocoa with Ruby, the joy of Cocoa meets the joy of Ruby. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Brian Marick]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/programming_cocoa_with_ruby.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Programming Erlang]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Learn how to write truly concurrent programs-programs that run on dozens or even hundreds of local and remote processors. See how to write high reliability applications even in the face of network and hardware failure using the Erlang programming language. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Joe Armstrong]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/programming_erlang.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Programming Groovy]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Groovy brings you the best of both worlds: a flexible, highly productive, agile, dynamic language that runs on the rich framework of the Java Platform. Groovy preserves the Java semantics and extends the JDK to give you true dynamic languagecapabilities programming in Groovyfeels like you are using an augmented Java. Programming Groovy will help you learn and take advantage of the latest version of this rich dynamic language, so you can be a more productive Java Platform developer. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Venkat Subramaniam]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/programming_groovy.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Programming Ruby 1.9, 3rd Edition]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Ruby is the fastest growing and most exciting dynamic language out there. If you need to get working programs delivered fast, you should add Ruby to your toolbox.
  
  This book is the only complete reference for Ruby 1.9, the very latest version of Ruby. (If you are still using Ruby 1.8, you'll want to check out the original PickAxe.) ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Dave Thomas, Chad Fowler, Andy Hunt]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/programming_ruby_1.9_3rd_edition.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Programming Ruby, 2nd Edition]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[The Pickaxe book, named for the tool on the cover, is the definitive reference to Ruby, a highly-regarded, fully object-oriented programming language. This Second Edition has more than 200 pages of new content, and substantial enhancements to the original, covering all the new and improved language features of Ruby 1.8 and standard library modules. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Dave Thomas, Chad Fowler, Andy Hunt]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/programming_ruby_2nd_edition.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Programming Scala]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Scala is an exciting, modern, multi-paradigm language for the JVM. You can use it to write traditional, imperative, object-oriented code. But you can also leverage its higher level of abstraction to take full advantage of modern, multicore systems. Programming Scala will show you how to use this powerful functional programming language to create highly scalable, highly concurrent applications on the Java Platform. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Venkat Subramaniam]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/programming_scala.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Prototype and script.aculo.us]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Tired of getting swamped in the nitty-gritty of cross-browser, Web 2.0-grade JavaScript? Get back in the game with Prototype and script.aculo.us, two extremely popular JavaScript libraries, that make it a walk in the park. Be it AJAX, drag and drop, auto-completion, advanced visual effects, or many other great features, all you need is to write one or two lines of script that look so good they could almost pass for Ruby code! ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Christophe Porteneuve]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/prototype_and_script.aculo.us.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Rails for .NET Developers]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Rails for .NET Developers introduces the joy of Ruby on Rails development to Microsoft .NET developers. This book demonstrates the essential elements of both the Ruby language and the Rails application framework, geared especially for developers already fluent in the Microsoft .NET platform. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Jeff Cohen, Brian Eng]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/rails_for_.net_developers.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Rails for PHP Developers]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Are you a PHP developer interested in the Ruby on Rails framework? Rails for PHP Developers kick-starts your Rails experience by guiding you through learning both Ruby and Rails from a PHP developer's perspective. Written by developers with deep experience using PHP, Ruby, and Rails, this book leverages your existing knowledge of PHP to learn Rails application development quickly and effectively. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Derek DeVries, Mike Naberezny]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/rails_for_php_developers.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Rails Recipes]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[You've read the tutorials and watched the online videos. You have a strong grasp of all of the ingredients that make up a successful Rails application. But ingredients don't just turn themselves into a meal. Chad Fowler's Rails Recipes is a collection of recipes that will take you step by step through the the most cutting edge Rails techniques, mixing the ingredients to create world-class web applications. Learn how to do it, and how to do it right. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Chad Fowler]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/rails_recipes.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Release It!]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Whether it's in Java, .NET, or Ruby on Rails, getting your application ready to ship is only half the battle. Did you design your system to survive a sudden rush of visitors from Digg or Slashdot? Or an influx of real world customers from 100 different countries? Are you ready for a world filled with flakey networks, tangled databases, and impatient users?
  
  If you are a developer and don't want to be on call at 3AM for the rest of your life, this book will help you. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Michael T. Nygard]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/release_it.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Scripted GUI Testing with Ruby]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[If you need to automatically test a user interface, this book is for you. Whether it's Windows, a Java platform (including Mac, Linux, and others) or a web app, you'll see how to test it reliably and repeatably.
  
  Many automated test frameworks promise the world and deliver nothing but headaches. Fortunately, you've got a secret weapon: Ruby. Ruby lets you build up a solution to fit your problem, rather than forcing your problem to fit into someone else's idea of testing.
  
  This book is for people who want to get their hands dirty on examples from the real world and who know that testing can be a joy when the tools don't get in the way. It starts with the mechanics of simulating button pushes and keystrokes, and builds up to writing clear code, organizing tests, and beyond. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Ian Dees]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/scripted_gui_testing_with_ruby.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Seven Languages in Seven Weeks]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[You should learn a programming language every year, as recommended by The Pragmatic Programmer. But if one per year is good, how about Seven Languages in Seven Weeks? In this book you'll get a hands-on tour of Clojure, Haskell, Io, Prolog, Scala, Erlang, and Ruby. Whether or not your favorite language is on that list, you'll broaden your perspective of programming by examining these languages side-by-side. You'll learn something new from each, and best of all, you'll learn how to learn a language quickly. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Bruce A. Tate]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/seven_languages_in_seven_weeks.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Ship It!]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Many software projects run into trouble, and many never ship at all. Others run like well-oiled machines. This book shows you the basics of how to get your project well on the road to success.
  
  Ship It! bucks current fashion trends and marketing hype; instead, you'll find page after page of solid advice, all tried and tested in the real world: a collection of tips that show you what tools a successful team has to use, and how to use them well. You'll get quick, easy-to-follow advice on modern techniques and when they should be applied. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Jared Richardson, Will Gwaltney, Jr]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/ship_it.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[SQL Antipatterns]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Bill Karwin has helped thousands of people write better SQL and build stronger relational databases. Now he's sharing his collection of antipatterns the most common errors he's identified in those thousands of requests for help.
  
  Most developers aren't SQL experts, and most of the SQL that gets used is inefficient, hard to maintain, and sometimes just plain wrong. This book shows you all the common mistakes, and then leads you through the best fixes. What's more, it shows you what's behind these fixes, so you'll learn a lot about relational databases along the way. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Bill Karwin]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/sql_antipatterns.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Stripes]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Tired of complicated Java web frameworks that just get in your way? Stripes is a lightweight, practical framework that lets you write lean and mean code without a bunch of XML configuration files. Stripes is designed to do a lot of the common work for you, while being flexible enough to adapt to your requirements. This book will show you how to use Stripes to its full potential, so that you can easily develop professional, full-featured web applications. As a bonus, you'll also get expert advice from the creator of Stripes, Tim Fennell. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Frederic Daoud]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/stripes.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Test Driven Development for Embedded C]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Still chasing bugs and watching your code deteriorate? Think TDD is only for desktop or web apps? It's not: TDD is for you, the embedded C programmer. TDD helps you prevent defects and build software with a long useful life. This is the first book to teach the hows and whys of TDD for C programmers. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[James W. Grenning]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/test_driven_development_for_embedded_c.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Test-Drive ASP.NET MVC]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[It's testable. It's light-weight. It's open-source. It's . . . Microsoft?
  
  Yes, finally, Microsoft has figured it out. ASP.NET MVC 2.0 lets you test drive your code, control the output of your HTML, and leverage C# and .NET in an easy-to-use web framework. This book shows you all you need to know to get started developing web applications using test-driven development (TDD). You'll learn how to do everything from creating your first test, to building REST web services, to deploying your finished ASP.NET MVC applications. Test-Drive ASP.NET MVC gets you started with all the fundamentals you need, whether you're transitioning from older Microsoft technologies, or if you're coming from an open-source background and are curious about what ASP.NET MVC has to offer. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Jonathan McCracken]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/test-drive_asp.net_mvc.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[TextMate]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[TextMate is a powerful tool for programmers, web designers, and anyone else who regularly needs to work with text files on Mac OS X. TextMate focuses on pragmatic automation, which means it will save you time-time that's always in short supply. See how your lowly text editor can become a hard working member of your staff. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[James Edward Gray II]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/textmate.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[The Agile Samurai]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Here are three simple truths about software development:
  
  1. You can't gather all the requirements up front.
  2. The requirements you do gather will change.
  3. There is always more to do than time and money will allow.
  
  Those are the facts of life. But you can deal with those facts (and more) by becoming a fierce software-delivery professional, capable of dispatching the most dire of software projects and the toughest delivery schedules with ease and grace. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Jonathan Rasmusson]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/the_agile_samurai.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[The Passionate Programmer, 2nd edition]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[This book is about creating a remarkable career in software development. In most cases, remarkable careers don't come by chance. They require thought, intention, action, and a willingness to change course when you've made mistakes. Most of us have been stumbling around letting our careers take us where they may. It's time to take control. This revised and updated second edition lays out a strategy for planning and creating a radically successful life in software development. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Chad Fowler]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/the_passionate_programmer_2nd_edition.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[The RSpec Book]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Behaviour-Driven Development (BDD) gives you the best of Test Driven Development, Domain Driven Design, and Acceptance Test Driven Planning techniques, so you can create better software with self-documenting, executable tests that bring users and developers together with a common language.
  
  Get the most out of BDD in Ruby with The RSpec Book, written by the lead developer of RSpec, David Chelimsky. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[David Chelimsky, Dave Astels, Zach Dennis, Aslak H]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/the_rspec_book.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[ThoughtWorks Anthology]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[This collection of essays covers a wide range of issues facing software developers today. In this book, you'll find a treasure trove of pragmatic advice to improve the effectiveness of your development efforts.
  
  You'll find essays on testing, controlling a project, the creation of domain specific languages, issues of build and deploy, programming languages, techniques for software development, and more! ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[ThoughtWorks]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/thoughtworks_anthology.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Ubuntu Kung Fu]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Ubuntu's rise to power has been rapid, historic and well-deserved. It's the best Linux distribution ever, but most people only use a fraction of its power. Award-winning Linux author Keir Thomas gets down and dirty with Ubuntu to provide over 300 concise tips that enhance productivity, avoid annoyances, and simply get the most from Ubuntu. You'll find many unique tips here that can't be found anywhere else. You'll also get a crash course in Ubuntu's flavor of system administration. Whether you're new to Linux or an old hand, you'll find tips to make your day easier. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Keir Thomas]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/ubuntu_kung_fu.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Using JRuby]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Now you can bring the best of Ruby into the world of Java, with Using JRuby. Come to the source for the JRuby core team's insights and insider tips. You'll learn how to call Java objects seamlessly from Ruby, and deal with Java idioms such as interfaces and overloaded functions. Run Ruby code from Java, and make a Java program scriptable in Ruby. See how to compile Ruby into .class files that are callable from Java, Scala, Clojure, or any other JVM language. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Charles O Nutter, Thomas Enebo, Nick Sieger, Ola B]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/using_jruby.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Web Design for Developers]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Web Design for Developers will show you how to make your web-based application look professionally designed. We'll help you learn how to pick the right colors and fonts, avoid costly interface and accessibility mistakes your application will really come alive. We'll also walk you through some common Photoshop and CSS techniques and work through a web site redesign, taking a new design from concept all the way to implementation. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Programmers]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Brian P. Hogan]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/web_design_for_developers.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Beginning Microsoft SQL Server 2008 Administration]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[SQL Server 2008 introduces many new features that will change database administration procedures; many DBAs will be forced to migrate to SQL Server 2008. This book teaches you how to develop the skills required to successfully administer a SQL Server 2008 database; no prior experience is required. The material covers system installation and configuration/architecting, implementing and monitoring security controls, configuring and managing network communications, automating administration tasks, disaster prevention and recovery, performance monitoring, optimizing and ensuring high availability, as well as major SQL Server 2008 components including Integration Services, Reporting Services, Analysis Services, and Service Broker. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[Wrox]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Chris Leiter, Dan Wood, Michael Cierkowski, Albert]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/beginning_microsoft_sql_server_2008_administration.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Microsoft SharePoint 2007 for Office 2007 Users]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Aimed at end users who face the daunting task of mastering MOSS 2007 in the enterprise business environment, this book shows you how to make effective use of what can be a confusing array of features. You?ll review how SharePoint is central to the Microsoft Office platform because organizations use it to organize workflow, integrate Office documents with line of business applications, provide search capabilities across all types of documents and data, and distribute these tools internally and externally on Web sites for end users. Plus, the book offers you well-designed examples and explanations that can be easily applied in real-world situations. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[Wrox]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Martin Reid]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/microsoft_sharepoint_2007_for_office_2007_users.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Microsoft SQL Server 2008 Administration with Windows PowerShell]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[The definitive guide to automating SQL Server admnistration with Powershell scripts
  
  If you're a SQL Server database administrator, this book will make your life easier. Windows PowerShell is an administrative scripting tool that allows you to automate many tasks you're probably currently doing by hand. This nuts-and-bolts guide shows you how to create Windows PowerShell scripts to administer almost every aspect of SQL Server.
  
  You'll get a thorough introduction to PowerShell basics and all the PowerShell components that have been integrated into SQL Server 2008, as well as actual administration tasks. The book provides complete scripts that have been tested and proven, saving you hours of effort. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[Wrox]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Ananthakumar Muthusamy, Yan Pan]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/microsoft_sql_server_2008_administration_with_windows_powershell.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Model-Driven Development with Executable UML]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[A comprehensive reference for an executable UML and the advantages of modeling This book presents the most up-to-date technology for rapidly developing information systems using the object-oriented paradigm and models, and establishes an executable profile of UML for such model-driven development. As a software developer, architect, or analyst, you'll benefit from learning how information systems can be developed more efficiently using the object-oriented paradigm and model-driven approach.
  
  Written by an expert who is uniquely qualified in the topic, this Wrox reference offers a profile of UML that is formal and executable, instead of the relational paradigm or its incomplete coupling with object orientation. It provides a comprehensive tutorial on model-driven development and UML. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[Wrox]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Dragan Milicev]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/model-driven_development_with_executable_uml.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[OpenSocial Network Programming]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[OpenSocial is a set of common application programming interfaces for Web-based social network applications. As the first book on OpenSocial, this valuable resource discusses the unique area of social networking and the needs and different attributes of social network applications. You ll get step-by-step instructions for creating OpenSocial applications for multiple platforms and explore application development and deployment using integration technologies like the new Sun Zembly Platform. Plus, you ll examine newer technologies like the Sun Platform that allows even non-programmers the ability to mash up applications. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[Wrox]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Lynne Grewe]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/opensocial_network_programming.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Professional ASP.NET MVC 1.0]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[This book begins with you working along as Scott Guthrie builds a complete ASP.NET MVC reference application. He begins NerdDinner by using the File->New Project menu command within Visual Studio to create a new ASP.NET MVC Application. You'll then incrementally add functionality and features. Along the way you'll cover how to create a database, build a model layer with business rule validations, implement listing/details data browsing, provide CRUD (Create, Update, Delete) data form entry support, implement efficient data paging, reuse UI using master pages and partials, secure the application using authentication and authorization, use AJAX to deliver dynamic updates and interactive map support, and implement automated unit testing.
  
  From there, the bulk of the rest of the book begins with the basic concepts around the model view controller pattern, including the little history and the state of the MVC on the web today. We'll then go into the ways that MVC is different from ASP.NET Web Forms. We'll explore the structure of a standard MVC application and see what you get out of the box. Next we dig deep into routing and see the role URLs play in your application. We'll deep dive into controllers and views and see what role the Ajax plays in your applications. The last third of the book focuses entirely on advanced techniques and extending the framework.  ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[Wrox]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Rob Conery, Scott Hanselman, Phil Haack, Scott Gut]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/professional_asp.net_mvc_1.0.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Professional DotNetNuke 5]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[DotNetNuke creator Shaun Walker leads this superlative author team of MVPs while delivering the latest update of a bestseller. They offer complete coverage of the major revisions to DotNetNuke 5, such as more granular administration, widgets, XHTML compliance, improved social networking, workflow, and better content management. They thoroughly cover installing, configuring, administering, and developing modules for DotNetNuke. You ll learn portal and host administration, configuration in a hosted environment, developing and working with modules, designing a DotNetNuke portal with skins, integrating workflow in DotNetNuke, using DotNetNuke social networking tools, and much more. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[Wrox]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Shaun Walker, Brian Scarbeau, Darrell Hardy, Stan ]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/professional_dotnetnuke_5.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Professional Microsoft Office SharePoint Designer 2007]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[With Professional Microsoft Office SharePoint Designer 2007, you can master all aspects of using Share Point Designer in an Enterprise environment to enhance Microsoft SharePoint Products and Technologies. Review key integration points, how to use CSS editing tools to create and modify SharePoint themes, how to supplement SharePoint Designer functionality by using Microsoft Visual Studio, and how to create a rich interactive experience. If you need to connect SharePoint with other enterprise resources or create components to integrate into the SharePoint framework, this book will show you how to accomplish these tasks. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[Wrox]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Woodrow W. Windischman, Bryan Phillips, Asif Rehma]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/professional_microsoft_office_sharepoint_designer_2007.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Professional Microsoft Robotics Developer Studio]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Microsoft Robotics Developer Studio (MRDS) offers an exciting new wayto program robots in the Windows environment. With key portions of the MRDS code available in source form, it is readily extensible and offers numerous opportunities for programmers and hobbyists. This comprehensive book illustrates creative ways to use the tools and libraries in MRDS so you can start building innovative new robotics applications.
  
  The book begins with a brief overview of MRDS and then launches into MRDS concepts and takes a look at fundamental code patterns that can be used in MRDS programming. You'll work through examples-all in C#-of common tasks, including an examination of the physics features of the MRDS simulator. As the chapters progress, so does the level of difficulty and you'll gradually evolve from navigating a simple robot around a simulated course to controlling simulated and actual robotic arms, and finally, to an autonomous robot that runs with an embedded PC or PDA. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[Wrox]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Kyle Johns, Trevor Taylor]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/professional_microsoft_robotics_developer_studio.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Professional Microsoft SQL Server 2008 Programming]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Master the increasingly complex feature set of the latest release of Microsoft SQL Server with the information in Professional Microsoft SQL Server 2008 Programming. Review the new features of SQL Server that will be of interest to you as an experienced developer and move on to more detailed, practical code examples. Learn how to write complex queries, build different types of data structures, improve application speed and performance, manage advanced scripting and errors, and design advanced databases the latest edition of this valuable programming guide. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[Wrox]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Robert Vieira]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/professional_microsoft_sql_server_2008_programming.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Professional Silverlight 2 for ASP.NET Developers]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Our overarching goal in writing this book was to give ASP.NET developers the power to quickly and easily create visually stunning Internet applications, coupled with rich interactivity to fully immerse the user in a new online experience. Silverlight gives you everything you need to do just this, and in serious style!
  
  As well as taking you through each feature that ships with Silverlight, this book will make sure you're able to debug, troubleshoot, and performance-tune your Silverlight applications, as well as seamlessly hook into your existing ASP.NET architecture and code base.
  
  This book is aimed at .NET developers and architects who want to quickly get up to speed with all that Silverlight 2 has to offer.
  
  As well as covering the breadth of features that Silverlight 2 provides, this book makes a point of demonstrating where necessary how the particular feature can be integrated tightly with the ASP.NET host application. An example is in Chapter 7, where the ASP.NET Profile service is utilized directly from within Silverlight to obtain user-specific data. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[Wrox]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Jonathan Swift, Salvador Alvarez Patuel, Chris Bar]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/professiona_silverlight_2_for_asp.net_developers.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Ruby on Rails for Microsoft Developers]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[This definitive guide examines how to take advantage of the new Agile methodologies offered when using Ruby on Rails (RoR). You'll quickly grasp the RoR methodology by focusing on the RoR development from the point of view of the beginner- to intermediate-level Microsoft developer. Plus, you'll get a reliable roadmap for migrating your applications, skill set, and development processes to the newer, more agile programming platform that RoR offers. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[Wrox]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Antonio Cangiano]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/ruby_on_rails_for_microsoft_developers.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Hackers]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Steven Levy's classic book about the original hackers of the computer revolution is now available in a special 25th anniversary edition, with updated material from noteworthy hackers such as Bill Gates, Mark Zuckerberg, Richard Stallman, and Steve Wozniak. Hackers traces the exploits of innovators from the research labs in the late 1950s to the rise of the home computer in the mid-1980s. It's a fascinating story for everyone interested in this seminal period in history. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[O'Reilly Media]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Steven Levy]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/hackers.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[PHP: The Good Parts]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Get past all the hype about PHP and dig into the real power of the language. This book explores the most useful features of PHP and how they can speed up the web development process, and explains why the most commonly used PHP elements are often misused or misapplied. You'll learn which parts add strength to object-oriented programming, and how to use certain features to integrate your application with databases. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[O'Reilly Media]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Peter MacIntyre]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/php_the_good_parts.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[The Art of SEO]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[If your company is going to succeed in the web economy, optimizing your site for search engine visibility is essential. In this book, four of the most noted experts in the field of search engine optimization (SEO) provide you with proven guidelines and cutting-edge techniques for planning and executing a comprehensive SEO strategy. The authors clearly explain SEO fundamentals, while correcting many common misconceptions. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[O'Reilly Media]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Eric Enge, Stephan Spencer, Rand Fishkin, Jessie C]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/the_art_of_seo.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Windows 7 Up and Running]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[This compact book offers the quickest path for Windows XP and Vista users to get started with Microsoft's Windows 7 operating system. With Windows 7: Up and Running, you get the essential information you need to upgrade or install the system and configure it to fit your activities, along with a tour of Windows 7's features and built-in applications. Windows 7 is poised to be a big hit among PC users, and with this handy guide, you can be productive with it right away. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[O'Reilly Media]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Wei-Meng Lee]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/windows_7_up_and_running.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Using Joomla]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[With Joomla, you don't need to have any technical expertise or web design experience to create effective websites and web apps. Whether you're creating your first website or building a multi-function site for a client, this book provides straightforward, hands-on instruction that makes it easy to learn this open source web content management system. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[O'Reilly Media]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Ron Severdia, Kenneth Crowder]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/using_joomla.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Effective UI]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[Effective UI provides a complete roadmap to building groundbreaking software centered on user experience (UX) quality, how to get management support, employing product management strategies proven to deliver greater success, and how to manage the design, engineering, staffing, and business considerations that must be centered on the user's needs and working effectively in tandem all throughout the project. Effective UI is a guide for business and product, software professionals, and anyone else struggling to advance the cause of better UX and working to deliver on the promise of higher quality software. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[O'Reilly Media]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Jonathan Anderson, John McRee, Robb Wilson, The Ef]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/effective_ui.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Fonts and Encodings]]></name>
		<description><![CDATA[This reference is a fascinating and complete guide to using fonts and typography on the Web and across a variety of operating systems and application software. Fonts & Encodings shows you how to take full advantage of the incredible number of typographic options available, with advanced material that covers everything from designing glyphs to developing software that creates and processes fonts. ]]></description>
		<publisher><![CDATA[O'Reilly Media]]></publisher>
		<author><![CDATA[Yannis Haralambous]]></author>
		<image><![CDATA[localhost/sachhay/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/fonts_and_encodings.jpg]]></image>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Programming]]></category>
		<download><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY]]></download>
	</node>
</data>
